nairatips.com 2017-11-21

# PRIVACY POLICY - NairaTips

It is part of Nairatips Privacy Policy to collect information from you when you register on our site. 

## **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)  
• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)  
• To process transactions 

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 

• **To send periodic emails**  
The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information  
We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us through through our email paularoloye@gmail.com
